{
  "title": "Pobre Ana 8-10 Vocab Words",
  "cards": [
    { "front": "despedirse", "back": "to say goodbye" },
    { "front": "visitaron", "back": "they visited" },
    { "front": "pasó", "back": "she/he spent or passed" },
    { "front": "supuestamente", "back": "supposedly" },
    { "front": "tenía miedo", "back": "was afraid" },
    { "front": "no le importaba", "back": "it didn't matter to him/her" },
    { "front": "se dan besos", "back": "gave each other kisses" },
    { "front": "solicitud de amistad", "back": "friend request" },
    { "front": "te envio", "back": "I'll send you" },
    { "front": "te la enviare", "back": "I will send it to you" },
    { "front": "tantas personas", "back": "so many people" },
    { "front": "no lo puede creer", "back": "She/He can't believe it." },
    { "front": "se sube", "back": "goes up/gets on" },
    { "front": "agradecida", "back": "thankful" },
    { "front": "no la ignoraban", "back": "they don't ignore her" },
    { "front": "compara", "back": "compares" },
    { "front": "cosas", "back": "things" },
    { "front": "mensaje", "back": "message" },
    { "front": "contigo", "back": "with you" },
    { "front": "conmigo", "back": "with me" },
    { "front": "vienes", "back": "you come" },
    { "front": "otra vez", "back": "again" },
    { "front": "creo que", "back": "I think/believe that" },
    { "front": "noticias", "back": "news" },
    { "front": "venir", "back": "to come" },
    { "front": "admiracion", "back": "admiration" },
    { "front": "importancia", "back": "importance" },
    { "front": "proyecto", "back": "project" },
    { "front": "desafortunadas", "back": "unfortunate" },
    { "front": "recoleccion", "back": "collection" },
    { "front": "contribuyen", "back": "they contribute/donate" },
    { "front": "distribuir", "back": "to distribute" },
    { "front": "entre", "back": "between" }
  ]
}
